Now switching to local news,
live from the Fulton
County Court House.
Miss Mclntyre. Can
we get a comment?
Were you surprised
with the jury's verdict?
I'm never surprised
at an acquittal.
And if you believe that,
there's a bridge north of here
you might be
interested in buying.
Hey, Kevin.
Hello.
Donuts get a bad rap.
Yeah, Greg, donuts are a
terribly misunderstood health food.
Look here, here's
your basic jelly donut.
Here's your fruit. Everybody
knows that fruit's good for you.
It's got your carbos.
You got to have carbos.
Mm, mm.
Who's the babe?
Some woman I saw the other day.
Lawyer. GREG: Pretty face.
- How's the rest of her?
- Good.
She works out four mornings a
week and at nights when she can.
- You dating her?
- No.
You know her?
Not yet.
There's a small matter
we need to discuss.
You didn't speak to Matthew Lyons.
He is now three weeks late on 200K.
He's paid us before.
Give him some slack.
Our employer is impatient.
He'd like you to make that
eminently clear to Mr. Lyons.
I want out, Greg.
You want out. The
boss won't like it.
What about the 150,000
a year you make tax-free?
And this house. How
you gonna rent it?
I can do without it. And
I'll take care of Mr. Lyons.
A couple of days.
This is the last one.
Fine. Just do it soon.
How much it set
you back at that gym?
- Fifty dollars a month.
- Fifty dollars a month?
That's about a
dollar-and-a-half a day.
You spend more than
that on a hot dog at lunch.
Fifty dollars a month. Whew.
- Dad, I came to ask you a favor.
- What?
If you don't mind, I would love
to give the closing argument.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
What you do at the that gym?
Well, I usually start out
with a stair-climbing machine.
I got stairs here.
You can run up and down them
for free. Save you $600 a year.
Then I ride the stationary bike.
What's the matter with
the bike I gave you?
You gave me that when I was 12.
This is state-of-the-art
equipment.
Boy, you're just kicking and screaming
your way into the '90s, aren't you?
- What are you talking about?
- You hate change.
Practically had to put you into
a headlock to get a computer.
You've been wearing
the same suit for 20 years.
I like my suit. Fits me perfect.
I know, all seven of them.
Dad, don't you think
it's time for a change?
No.
That suit is outdated.
You are so much more energetic
and vibrant than that suit gives off.
No. I'm not.
Come on, Dad. Let
me take you shopping.
- Please. We'll buy you a new suit.
- I hate to go shopping.
And they don't make
suits like mine anymore.
No argument there.
Yes. I'd like to report
a robbery, please.
Leanne!
Here, Pop.
Leanne.
- Pop.
- Oh. Are you all right?
Yeah. They took my jewelry and that
silver frame with the picture of us in it.
- That's okay.
- No, it's not.
Ben, listen, who knows,
maybe we'll get lucky.
Great.
Stay at my house tonight.
I'll let you run up and
down the stairs free.
I'll be okay, Dad, they're
not going to come back.
Before I go, would you take one last
look at this inventory of things taken?
Yeah, I think that's it.
March fourth.
I read a poem today by a
poet named James Kavanaugh.
It was about friendship.
There was a passage in
it that really touched me.
"Will you be my friend?
A friend
Who far beyond the
feebleness Of any vow or tie
Will touch the secret
place Where I am really I
To know the pain of lips
that plead And eyes that weep
Who will not run away
When you find me in the street
Will you be my friend?
The police didn't find any cash
in the defendant's possession
when they searched his car.
The defendant's fingerprints were
not found in the Crestmoor Bank.
In fact, there is not one
shred of forensic evidence
that places the defendant
anywhere near the Crestmoor Bank
on the night of the robbery.
So I have to ask you:
Is there reasonable doubt that
the defendant committed this crime?
I think there's plenty of it.
Ladies and gentlemen of the
jury, it is now time for the judge
to instruct you in the law
that applies to this case.
Who taught you how to
give a closing argument?
- You did.
- No wonder I liked it so much.
Leanne Mclntyre, Kevin Gilliam.
I'm sorry. Do we
know each other?
Did you get the message I left on
your answering machine at home?
No, I didn't. And if you're looking for
an attorney, now isn't a good time...
No, no. I'm a writer. I'm doing an
article for Georgia Today magazine
called Women In The Courtroom.
I'm profiling some of Atlanta's
prominent female attorneys,
and I was hoping you'd
let me interview you.
Georgia Today.
- Mister...?
- Gilliam.
What I was about to say,
Mr. Gilliam, is this isn't a good time
for me to commit to anything
right now. I'm very busy.
No problem. Why don't I
call you in a day or two?
- Maybe things will have eased up.
- That'll be fine.
- Okay. It was nice meeting you both.
- Nice meeting you.
Georgia Today.
That's top drawer.
We'll see, Pop.
- Wanna go shopping?
- You wanna go shopping?
Well, I found a silver picture
frame like that one that was taken,
and I thought I'd get it for
you, maybe cheer you up.
I love you, Pop.
But you know what? I feel like if I
start replacing the things that were taken,
I'm just admitting that I've given up
hope of ever getting anything back.
Well... I guess I
can understand that.
- You really wanna cheer me up?
- You know I do.
Great. Let's go
buy you a new suit.
That'd just thrill me.
Oh.
This is a nice one.
Too heavy. Make me sweat.
Why do you hate this so much?
Well, first of all, I
don't need a new suit.
Here we go.
And I have to go in one of
these little rooms and try it on.
They got pins all over the
floor and these little doors.
The doors on the
dressing room bother you?
They come down to my knees,
and you know I've got chicken legs.
- You have great legs.
- Can I be of some assistance?
- What kind of suit are you looking for?
- Something that won't wrinkle.
My dad is a
conservative dresser.
Do you have anything in a classic cut?
Maybe a dark wool blend of some kind.
You know, we just got
in the most fabulous suit.
Aah...
Rudolfo Stefanelli.
In my opinion, the finest
designer in Europe today.
What do you think?
I paid less for my first house.
- I think you'll love this cut.
- What is it?
Half off.
Try this on right now.
September ninth.
I had the most
bizarre reaction today.
I was in Tattinger's
Lingerie Shop
and I was staring at the sexiest
piece of lingerie I think I'd ever seen.
Six hundred dollars.
I almost bought it too.
But there is this little voice
inside of me that kept saying:
"Leanne, there is something
wrong with a woman
buying herself
expensive lingerie."
Okay, okay, okay, you
drive a hard bargain,
I'll only write glowing
things about you,
and I'll list your age as five
years younger than you really are.
- You remember me, don't you?
- Well, it's hard not to.
You happen to be wearing
my favorite men's cologne.
See? We're compatible.
Come on, Leanne,
let me interview you.
How long will this take?
It depends on how completely
and thoroughly engaging you are.
Great. That'll be short.
- Leanne!
- I'm right here, Dad.
- Jury's in.
- I'll be right there.
I can do it. How
about 3 this afternoon?
Perfect. It's a
beautiful day out.
- Let's say we meet at Freiman Park?
- Great.
Yeah. I'll pick up some
pastries. Do you like Linzer torte?
Excuse me?
I was asking you if
you liked Linzer torte?
I make Linzer torte.
It's my favorite dessert.
How about that?
Well, I'll see you around 3.
That's amazing.
Members of the jury,
have you reached a verdict?
We have, Your Honor.
We find the defendant,
Steven Dixon, guilty.
The defendant will return
to this courtroom at 9:00
on the tenth of this
month for sentencing.
This court is adjourned.
I guess I oversold
the Linzer torte.
You know, I probably
should have postponed this.
Do you always get this
upset when you lose?
Only when I'm sure
my client didn't do it.
- You really care, don't you?
- Yeah.
Has anyone ever told you
you have beautiful skin?
Thank you.
Great eyes.
It must be difficult for you
to have much of a social life
with the heavy work
schedule you keep.
Well, I make time for the
things that are important to me.
Does that mean you're
dating anyone regularly?
Are you doing an
article on me as a lawyer,
- or are you coming on to me?
- It was just a question.
No. It wasn't just a
question. It was a pass.
And I really don't appreciate you
misrepresenting yourself to me.
- Leanne, I wasn't coming on to you.
- You know what, Kevin,
the interview is
over. Enjoy the torte.
So where have you been all day?
Catching up on some errands.
Nice threads.
Cologne. Have a
hot date, my man?
Yeah, I had a date. Kind of.
Why do I feel like
you're wasting your time?
You're writing your memoirs.
I stole her diary.
You're not a burglar.
I want to know everything
I can about Leanne.
- Leanne?
- Yes. Mclntyre.
Why do you want to know so
much about Leanne Mclntyre?
It's important to me.
How's Mr. Lyons feeling?
I haven't done it.
I know.
I told you I would do
it this one last time.
You tell the boss
I want to be clean.
Forget the girl, Kev.
And don't bite the
hand that feeds you.
Mr. Lyons.
I'll have it all in 48
hours. No problem.
I promise.
You give me half of it now,
maybe it could buy you some time.
Tell him I'll have
the money Thursday.
I don't want to hurt you.
I don't have it, Kevin. Please.
I gotta break something.
Don't.
- I got my orders, I'm sorry.
- I'll have the money in 48 hours.
Can we start this over again?
I hated what happened today.
- This really isn't necessary.
- Yes, it is.
Because I was coming on to you.
I guess I was just overwhelmed
with this attraction I was feeling for you
and, ahem, heh, I
responded badly.
Would you like to come in?
Thank you.
If I'd known I was
going to upset you...
No. It was just bad timing.
And I probably overreacted too.
It's just been a
rough couple of days.
Something you can talk about?
Want to sit down?
My place was
burglarized the other day.
Oh, um...
- I'm sorry.
- The insurance will reimburse me.
Mostly took costume jewelry.
Nothing worth much except for a
couple of pieces my mom gave me.
And those I'll never replace.
And then last night, I discovered
that my diary was gone.
- You think it was stolen?
- Well, it's missing.
I keep it in that
drawer every night.
Anyway, enough about that.
Looks like a book.
Shall I open it?
Absolutely. It's one
of my favorite poets.
- James Kavanaugh.
- You've heard of him?
Oh!
I love this man's work. I
can't believe you know him.
Thank you.
You're very welcome.
You want to stay for dinner?
I was just making myself
a salad. It'll feed five.
I have a better idea.
Let me take you out to dinner.
I promise I'll behave, and
we can do the interview.
Okay.
- Let me just go change.
- Take your time.
- Damn it!
- Are you okay?
Leanne?
Is everything all right?
- It's gone.
- What?
My grandmother's brooch.
She gave it to me
on my 16th birthday.
I'm sorry.
It was on this jacket.
It was the first piece of jewelry
my grandfather ever bought for her.
Wow.
This guy's really
changed my life.
Changes the way I breathe
when I walk into my own house,
the way I sleep,
the way I think.
What kind of person does this?
Do you think juries
look at you differently
than they do male trial lawyers?
Some do. There's no question.
When my dad is attacking
a witness' testimony,
I love to watch
the jury's faces.
They seem almost
mesmerized sometimes.
I can't act like that.
Juries don't like that kind of
aggressiveness in a woman.
It's not feminine.
I can see that in their faces.
Don't you resent that?
Yes, but I let it go.
You wanna know a secret?
I try to act like my dad.
Sometimes it works, and
sometimes I just can't pull it off.
Okay. So, you must be getting
bored, hearing me go on about myself.
Hardly.
What about you? Did you
always want to be a writer?
No one grows up dreaming of being
a writer for Georgia Today magazine.
Okay. So, what did you
want to be when you grew up?
You won't laugh?
- An actor.
- Are you serious?
You didn't see Phantom?
You were in Phantom
of the Opera?
No.
But I did sing in a
production of The Magic Flute
in Sewickley, Pennsylvania.
What are you smiling about?
- Gonna do it again.
- Do what?
I can't believe this. I
feel like a school kid.
I wanted to hold your hand.
- Mr. Lyons squared up today.
- Good.
I told you I'd take care of
Mr. Lyons, and I did that.
- Now I'm through.
- What the hell's wrong with you?
- Are you nuts?
- Maybe.
You're a thug, Kevin.
She's a lawyer, a lawyer
whose house you ripped off.
Do you think you're
gonna marry her now?
No. Consider me retired.
Giving up the business,
are we? Going straight?
Get out of here, Greg.
You made 150K last year, tiger,
what are you gonna do, wait tables?
You need a shrink, man.
Well, I'll see you in a couple
of hours. I got a bail hearing.
I won't be here. I'm going
to meet Kevin at the beach.
Boy, that must be some
long article he's writing.
Where's your new suit?
In my closet.
- Why?
- It's where I keep all my new suits.
Dad.
We bought that
suit for a reason.
That's right, to cheer you
up, and you do seem happier.
Go on, Dad. Go on
upstairs and change.
My client is an exemplary
member of this community,
and he has been unjustly
accused of these charges.
- Mr. Matlock.
- Yes, sir?
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine, sir.
You... You look different.
- For the better or the worse?
- Not sure.
I saw you in the hall and
didn't know who you were.
I had to ask somebody.
- Proceed.
- Yes, sir.
Uh, as I was saying, my
client is an exemplary member
of this community and there's
no reason in the world to believe
there's any...
danger of flight.
He has lived in the
same house for 15 years,
held the same job for ten years,
and he's anxious to come into this
court so he can clear his good name.
Excuse me, just a second.
What's the matter with you,
Mr. Matlock? Is something wrong?
Your Honor, can I just
have a ten minute recess?
During a bail hearing?
Five minutes. I'll be right
back before you know it.
All right.
This court will remain
in recess for five minutes.
Oh.
Yeah, that's why I didn't
know you, Mr. Matlock.
- Yes, sir.
- You okay now?
All perfect, just
like my old self.
As I was saying...
I'll give you five dollars
if we can stop running.
Come on, 5O more
yards, big finish, let's go.
Come on.
I gotta stop. You're killing me.
Tell me you thought
that was exhilarating.
That was exhausting. I
gotta get something to drink.
Come on, we'll call the
paramedics from over there.
I'll race you. Come on.
- Hello.
- Two, please.
This way.
We gotta get out of here. He's
one of the biggest bores I ever met.
- If we sit, he'll never leave us alone.
- All right.
Thanks, anyway.
- Is something wrong?
- No.
You were so quiet at dinner.
You seemed sort of sad.
I'm sorry.
Maybe it's the realization that my
dreams of winning the decathlon
were shattered
today on that beach.
- Wanna come in?
- I should go. It's late.
Cup of decaf? We
could talk a while.
- About what?
- This and that.
This and that
can take all night.
- What's wrong?
- It's complicated.
Are you married?
If it were only that simple.
Well, what is it?
This wasn't a
good idea. I'm sorry.
- Pop.
- Hi.
How was dinner last night?
I'm gonna save you a
whole lot of questions.
I don't think I'm gonna
be seeing Kevin anymore.
What happened?
Well...
What are you doing?
Um, I'm, uh... I'm
taking a suit back.
Why?
- It didn't work out.
- It didn't work out?
What does that
mean? Doesn't fit?
It fits. It just doesn't fit me.
- You can't take it back.
- I only wore it once.
They altered it.
I'll rip out the stitches.
It'll be like new.
I bought you something.
- What's this for?
- Nothing. Just...
Oh, Dad, you didn't have
to replace the picture frame.
I know you didn't want
to start replacing things.
But I just thought...
Thank you.
Well, what do you know?
I read a poem today by a
poet named James Kavanaugh.
It was about friendship.
Looks like a book.
Shall I open it?
Absolutely. He's one
of my favorite poets.
- James Kavanaugh.
- You've heard of him?
I love this man's work. I
can't believe you know him.
Bundled up in Grandma's
comforter, drinking hot chocolate,
eating my homemade Linzer torte.
It's a beautiful day. How
about we meet at Freiman Park?
- Great.
- I'll pick up some pastries.
- Do you like Linzer torte?
- Excuse me?
I was asking you if
you liked Linzer torte.
Are you married?
If it were only that simple.
Well, what is it?
This wasn't a good idea.
I'm sorry.
Yes, please, could I have the
number of Georgia Today magazine?
What the hell? Gee.
Leanne.
I want my jewelry back.
You're very good. Make a date with me
at the park, so you can follow me here.
That's a side of you I
would never have guessed.
Maybe if you'd read my entire
diary, this wouldn't have come
as such a surprise to you.
I never read your diary.
I must have gone through that
drawer a dozen times looking for it.
Tell me something.
Did you use the key that I hide
outside the door to put it back?
I wanted to mention to you I
called Georgia Today magazine.
Nobody there has
ever heard of you.
I'm not surprised. I'm writing
the article on speculation.
You're a liar.
I went back to that
cafe at the beach,
found out who the man
was with the broken hand.
How do you live with yourself?
Leanne.
Let me just... Let me just
make sure I've got this straight.
In your off hours, you
break into women's homes,
rip off their diaries, and then try to
become the man you think they want?
That's completely
untrue, Leanne.
Leanne.
When were you
gonna give this to me?
Excuse me?
You know damn well I wrote about
lingerie from Tattinger's in my diary.
When were you
gonna give this to me?
Well, I...
I'm coming after you.
I don't care how
long it takes me.
I'm gonna get you for
breaking into my home.
- Leanne.
- Oh.
Your concern overwhelms me.
It was all just a game
for you, wasn't it?
Leanne, Leanne.
Before you go, think about this.
If it was just a game, why
didn't I spend the night with you?
Remember, "talking
about this and that"?
I could have, you know.
- Hi.
- Hi, Dad.
I thought you might be here.
- How you doing?
- I'll be okay.
I found something of yours
this morning at my house.
Grandma's brooch.
Where did you find it?
The couch. It must have fallen
down between the cushions.
But, Dad, I haven't
worn this brooch to your...
to your house in months.
What say we go home?
Can we walk for a while?
www.tvsubtitles.net